# TRI AJI RAMADHAN

# FULLSTACK DEVELOPER | PHYSICS TUTOR

# CONTACT DETAILS

Address: Gg. Karya III RT07/RW09 No. 12, Menteng Atas, Keca Setia Budi, Jakarta Selatan

Contact: +62 857 4758 9814
Email: triajidhan@gmail.com
Instagram: @ramadhantriaji
Linked In: Tri Aji Ramadhan

**Github**: https://github.com/triajidhan **Portfolio**: https://triajidhan.github.io/

# SHORT PROFILE

I am a physics tutor with more than two years of experience teaching, both remote and offline. I use different learning stages for each student, depending on the student's level of understanding. I'm also a web developer who focuses on frontend developers.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Physics Tutor**

# One Learning Center | Contract | December 2019 - June 2022

- Teaching physics using national, national+ or Cambridge Curriculum depending on the student's school (remote and offline)
- Some of my students come from SMAK 1 Penabur and St Laurencia

## Video Solution Maker

# Co-learn | Part-time | June 2021 - December 2021

- · Create video solutions of physics subject for junior high, senior high, and UTBK level
- Award: Best video of the month (on October, 2021)

# EDUCATION

## 2015 - 2019 • Diponegoro University

### **Material Physics**

Departement of Physics, Science and Matematics Faculty | Diponegoro University Bachelor of Science

Ungradutate Thesis: "Numerical Analysist of Electric Polarization in Ferroelectric Thin-Film" by MATLAB

#### 2012 - 2015 • SMA N 1 Kesesi

## **Natural Science**

Third best graduate of natural science study program
Third place in the 2014 Pekalongan district physics OSN selection

# LICENSES & CERTIFICATIONS

#### SoloLearn.com

June 2022 | HTML, CSS, Javascript & JQuery

#### Lawencon International

Agust 2022 - now | Fullstack Developer Java

## SKILLSHEETS

## HARD SKILLS

Markup Languages: HTML, CSS

Programming Languages: Javascript, Java

**Library**: ReactJS, JQuery **Frameworks**: Bootstrap

Rest API

Version Control System (VCS): Git, Github

**Database Management System (DBMS)**: MySQL, Postgresql **Graphic Design**: Corel Draw, Photoshop, Infinite Design

Basic Computer: MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint

**Audio Editor**: Adobe Audition **Video Editor**: Kinemaster

#### SOFT SKILLS

Teamwork
Communication
Adaptability
Problem-solving
Creativity
Leadership

# LANGUAGES

indonesia: Native or bilingual proficiency

English: Limited working proficiency (TOEFL: 417 | 2018)

## INTEREST

In my sphere time, I personality enjoy learning about phyhsics, frontend developer and digital painting to upgrade my skills.